Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 19.04.11 11:26:30
-=THE LAST FANTASY=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=TLF字幕组=- 译校：gazagoal
# Holdin' hands at midnight 'neath a starry sky #
# Nice work if you can get it #
# And you can get it if you try #
# Strollin' with that one girl, sighin' sigh after sigh #
# Nice work if you can get it #
# And you can get it if you try #
# Just imagine someone waitin' at the cottage door #
# Where two hearts become one #
- # Who could ask for anything more? # - Mmm!
秀色可餐
That looks good enough to eat.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
不是说蛋糕
I wasn't talking about the cake.
戈登，你是我表弟
Oh, Gordon. You're my cousin.
皇室不都这样吗
Never stopped the Royal Family.
你真恶心
You're a very sick man.
嗨
Mm. Hi.
-嗨 -可人儿
- Hi. - You're yummy.
妈妈，送奶奶去教堂好吗？
Oh, Mum, would you take Grandma over to the church, please?
好，走吧，甜心儿
Yes. Come on, sweetheart.
去叫丹尼斯，说我们准备好了
So, do you wanna go and tell Dennis that we're ready?
收到
Sure thing.
他怎么样？
How's he doing?
很好，乐癫儿了
Oh, great. Thrilled.
真的，乐颠儿了
I'm telling you, he's thrilled.
丹尼斯，是戈登，准备好了？
Dennis, it's Gordon. Are you ready?
哇，你太帅了！
Wow! You look great!
准备好了？
So, are you ready?
呃…
Um...
-再… -好
- Just... - OK.
再给你一分钟…
I'm gonna give you a minute to, uh...
一分钟
give you a minute.
不，我不…
No, no. I don't want to.
不想啊…
Done want to, ah...
丹尼斯！
Dennis!
丹尼斯，到时间了
It's time. Dennis, we have to go.
丹尼斯！
Dennis!
# Where to promise to love one... #
丹尼斯，我们要有孩子了
Dennis, we're gonna have a baby.
丹尼斯
Dennis.
丹尼斯？
Dennis?
# Who could ask for anything more? #
该死
Aw, shit.
丹尼斯！
Dennis!
# I'm sorry, sorry, sorry if you're gettin' me wrong #
# But you're half a world away with only one sock on #
# Now you're gettin' too much, I don't want to play along #
# 'Cause all I really wanted was a radio song #
片名： 《胖男孩快跑》
# What is there to say #
# What is there to say?
# In a world so grey? #
# In a world so grey #
# Why, oh, why, oh, why are we singing it anyway? #
五年后
别跑了！
- Come on! - # 'Cause you think I had #
停下！
- # A wind-up heart # - Stop!
回来！
- # Then you must have had plastic head # - Come back!
让我喘口气！
- # Did you think I had to play the part? # - Give me a break!
# When you copied everything I said? #
- # When the tide of love is out and the rust begins to show # - Whoo!
# You're cryin' in your sleep #
# Scared of your shadow #
- # If you thought this was forever # - Ooh!
- Oh! - # Dear, I'm keeping you in mind #
藏哪儿了？
Gotcha. Where is it?
什么东西？
Where's what?
你知道！
You know what I'm talkin' about!
Ooh! Hey! Hey!
干什么！
Ooh!
这你怎么说？
All right!
我从来没见过
What do you think this is, huh?
你还真能跑
I've never seen those before in my life.
Yeah, and you're a fit, running type.
王八蛋
You bastard.
住嘴
Don't.
小兔崽子！
Little shit!
没什么好看的，大伙
There's nothing to see here, people.
Ow!
胸罩呢？
Where's the bra?
什么胸罩？
What bra?
来，胖哥哥，跑啊
Whoo!
Come on, fat boy, run!
我不胖！
I'm not fat!
我只是…不瘦
I'm just... I'm unfit.
去啊
Go on, then.
Ow!
谁？
Yes?
能开门吗，古先生
Could you let me in, please, Mr G?
你他娘是谁？
Who the hell are you?
你…干嘛这…
You... Why are we...
楼下的丹尼斯・道尔
It's Dennis Doyle from downstairs.
楼下的丹尼斯・道尔已经死了
Dennis Doyle from downstairs is dead...
被房东干掉了
killed by his landlord.
-知道为什么吗？ -不
- Do you know why? - No.
房租付晚了
Failure to pay the rent in a timely fashion.
丹尼斯！
Dennis!
玛雅，能不能让你爸…
Hey, Maya. Listen, can you tell your dad...
我有点急事
I'm in a bit of a hurry?
-你有钱了吗？ -玛雅，回去
- Have you got any money? - Maya, go inside!
穿上点衣服
And put something on.
嘿，嘿
Hello. Hello.
啊？
Yes?
知道房东杀了楼下的丹尼斯・道尔 之后怎样了？
Do you know what happened to that landlord...
after he killed Dennis Doyle from downstairs?
-不 -获奖了
- No. - They gave him a medal...
还享受了一顿脚底按摩
and a nice foot massage.
嘿，古施达施迪达赫先生
Hey, Mr Ghoshdashtidar.
古施达施迪达赫先生，等等…
Mr Ghoshdashtidar, wait...
老家伙怎么样了？
Well, how is the old rascal?
听说这次宴会十分盛大
I hear it's going to be a party of special magnificence.
你也了解比尔博
You know Bilbo.
他吊足了大家的胃口
He's got the whole place in an uproar.
这样他才高兴
Mm. Ah, well, that should please him.
杰克，你爸马上就来
Jake, your dad's gonna be here in a minute.
准备好了？
You ready?
好了！
Ready!
好吧，但要保住秘密
All right, then keep your secrets.
嗨
Hey.
- # You give me tone # - Hey.
# I'll like that #
嗨，怎样？
Hey, how is it goin'?
是吗
- Oh, yeah. - # All the chrome #
# Well, I'll like that #
丹尼斯，对，丹尼斯
Dennis. Yeah, Dennis.
一起…喝一杯怎么样？
# Do you run away? #
You like, uh, to have some sort of drink with me?
管他呢…
Oh, what the hell. Let's...
Ow, shit!
Oh!
- Hah! - Aah!
喔，被你刺中了！
No. Oh, you got me!
-嗨 -嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
我们在玩霍比特人大战半兽人
- We're playing hobbits and orcs. - Mm-hmm.
猜谁是半兽人？
Guess who's an orc?
宝贝，能不能麻烦…
Honey, would you mind, uh...
有点疼，麻烦你？
This kind of smarts. Can you?
谢谢
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
还没玩完呢，威特！
I'm not finished with you, Whit!
这就来
Yeah, one sec.
他爸爸不是来接他吗？
Uh, I thought his dad was picking him up.
-出什么事了？ -什么事？
- What happened? - Oh, what happened?
丹尼斯的事
Dennis happened.
不过也有好事
Mmm. Well, on the bright side...
-嗯？ -你今天特别地美
- Hmm? - You look astonishingly beautiful today.
-威特！ -真的
- Whit! - Really.
你干什么去了？
Where have you been?
嗨
Hey.
-我… -爸！
- I was... - Daddy!
小鼻涕孩儿！
Hey, snot-face!
别这么叫他
Oh, please, don't call him that.
怎么了？他不是鼻涕孩儿吗？
Why? He is a snot-face, isn't he?
你是小鼻涕孩儿，对不？
You are a snot-face, aren't you? Huh?
Oh.
杰克，好恶心
Aw!
Jake, that's disgusting.
杰克，很恶心，去吧
Jake, that's disgusting. Go on.
-先上厕所 -妈！
- Toilet first. - Mom!
去，穿上外套
Go on. Grab your jacket.
你应该一个小时前到的
You were supposed to be here an hour ago, Dennis.
对，但…票有点小问题，所以
Yeah, there was a bit of a mix-up with the...
with the tickets, so...
你真漂亮
Hey, you look really nice.
那项链是我买的？
Did I get you that necklace?
不，是…
No. It was a...
别人送我的
just a present from someone... else.
-谁？ -我
- Who? - Uh, me, actually.
是
Oh, yeah.
啊？
Huh?
我奶奶传下来的
It belonged to my grandmother.
是啊
Yeah.
啊？
Huh?
丹尼斯，这是我的好朋友，威特
Dennis, this is my good friend, Whit.
威特，这是我…儿子的爹，丹尼斯
Whit, this is my... Jake's dad, Dennis.
你好吗？
How you doin'?
好，手很软
Good, yeah. You have soft hands.
你抹手霜？
Do you moisturize?
是的
I do, actually.
认识你很高兴
Well, it's very nice to meet you.
很高兴能把人和名字联系上
It's nice to finally put a face to the name.
我以为你…
I'd have probably thought you'd have...
应该看过我俩的照片
you would have seen one of our photos.
都没了
Oh, there aren't any.
走吗？
- Hmm. - Ready?
走
Yes. Let's go.
-玩的开心 -嗯
- Have fun. - Yeah.
丹尼斯，你有票吗？
Dennis, you do have the tickets, right?
丽碧，相信我的智商
Libby, credit me with some intelligence.
票
Tickets!
谁有票？
Does anybody have any tickets?
哥们，我女儿生病了
Mate, my daughter's not very well.
你想要的话我这儿有几张
I've got a couple of spare tickets if you want 'em.
好，谢谢，多少钱？
Yes. Thank you so much. How much?
你看着给
Oh, whatever.
我就这些钱了
Uh, this is all the money I have.
行吗？
Yeah?
我儿子肯定爱死我了
My son is gonna love me.
希望儿子爱你？那就别犯法
You want your son to love you? Don't break the law.
你这是下套诱捕！
Hey, that's entrapment!
Oh, God!
这是滥用暴力！
And that's brutality!
丽碧，只是警告一下
Libby, it's... It was only a caution.
不，丽碧，我…
No. Uh, Libby, I'll...
-拜，爸 -丽碧
- Bye, Dad. - Libby.
你和丽碧一起在糕点店工作？
So, do you work with Libby at the bakery?
不
No.
我们倒是在糕点店认识的
We met at the bakery, though.
-是吗？ -是啊
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
怎么了？
What?
没什么，想起来那天我紧张得很
No, I just was a nervous wreck that day.
买了四个巧克力小饼
It took me four chocolate eclairs...
一个甜饼才鼓起勇气搭讪
and a macaroon just to get up the courage to talk to her.
其实我在金融区工作
Uh, no, I work in the financial district actually.
我是沃特曼・休斯公司的对冲基金经理
I'm a hedge fund manager for Waterman Hughes.
哦
Oh.
我在一家高档零售商店 做高级安全分析与实践
I do high-level security analysis and operation...
for an upscale retail outlet.
真的？
Really?
丽碧说你是女服专卖店的保安
Libby said you were a security guard...
我说的就是这个
at a women's clothing store.
Yeah, that's what I said.
对
Right.
我先打车走了
Uh, well, l... I should probably get a cab.
明天早上还要长跑呢
I got a big run in the morning.
长什么？
A big what?
跑，为下个月的耐克环河赛做训练
A run... I'm training for the Nike River Run next month.
什么？
The what-y what what?
耐克环河赛
The Nike River Run.
环绕泰晤士河的马拉松比赛
It's a... It's a marathon race along the, uh, Thames River.
你跑这个干什么？
Why would you do that?
是个慈善比赛
Uh, well, it's a charity thing, you know?
而且我喜欢跑步
Plus, I love to run.
我之前还参加了伦敦马拉松
I actually ran the London Marathon a little while ago.
真巧啊
Oh, that's a coincidence.
怎么说？
Oh, yeah? How's that?
我看转播了
I watched it on the television.
就看了最后一小时
- Ah. - Well, the last hour.
我星期天起得晚，所以…
I sleep in on a Sunday, so...
是啊
Right.
你看
Um, well, look, you know...
我知道这样挺尴尬的
I know these things can be pretty awkward, you know?
你是杰克的父亲
I mean, you know, you're Jake's dad...
我只是希望你明白
and, uh, well, I just want you to know...
我十分喜欢丽碧和杰克
that I like Libby and Jake very, very much...
我很感激你对此事如此理智
and, um, well, I just appreciate your being so grown up...
about this, you know?
嘿！
Hey! Yo!
你乘这辆？
You wanna take this one?
-不，你走吧 -确定？
- No, you have it. - You sure?
是，我再叫一辆
Yeah. I'll get the next one.
好，跟你聊天很高兴
All right. Very nice to meet you.
-是啊 -以后还会见面的
- Yeah. - I'm sure I'll see you around.
恩，倒想
Yup. Hope so.
好先生，请到西印度码头
Hello, good sir. West India Quay, please.
-拜 -拜拜
- Bye. - Bye.
-再见 -拜拜
- See ya. - Bye-bye.
丹尼斯！
Dennis!
丹尼斯？
Dennis?
-闭上眼睛 -啊？
- Close your eyes. - Huh?
-闭上眼睛 -哦
- Close your eyes. - Oh.
睁开吧，情人节快乐
OK. Open them. Happy Valentine's.
真好
That's great.
丹尼斯！
Dennis!
嗨
Hi.
嘿，文森特
Hey, Vincent.
-丹尼斯 -生意如何？
- Dennis. - How's business?
生意个啥？
Whatcha mean, "business"?
抱歉
Sorry.
-下注 -嘘
- Got it. - Shh.
别说话
Hush now, man.
好
All right.
三千
Three thousand.
我就这些
This is all I've got.
都压上
Just throw whatever you have in the pot.
好
OK.
同花，K
Flush, king high.
A
Ace high.
怎么了？
What happened?
运气不好啊
Bad luck, mate.
Oh.
票买到了
Oh, hey, I got you those tickets.
那是昨天的
They were for yesterday.
怎么？你不要了？
What? So now you don't want 'em?
我要它干什么？
Why would I want them?
上易趣网卖了
Put them on eBay.
谁想买昨天的票？
Who's gonna wanna buy tickets...
for something that happened yesterday?
-时空旅行家 -你昨天干什么去了？
- Time travellers. - Where were you?
整晚都毁了
My whole night was just screwed, man...
我在丽碧的新男友面前像个傻蛋
and I looked like a prick in front of Libby's new boyfriend.
她没告诉我她交新男友了
Oh, she didn't tell me she has a new boyfriend.
那人怎么样？
What's he like?
帅，有钱，绅士
Handsome, well-off, friendly.
好像古怪赛车里的完美皮特
He's like Peter Perfect out of Wacky Races...
还跑马拉松
and he runs marathons.
-跑那干嘛？ -就是嘛
- Why? - Exactly.
我惟一一次表白的回应…
Well, look, my only serious relationship ended...
是口吐白沫，抽搐倒地
in a broken collarbone and a dead meerkat...
所以我劝你没什么说服力
so I may not be the best person in the world to give advice...
但你联系了丽碧五年了
but you have been trying to get through to Libby...
for five years now...
也许你该放手了
so maybe you should let her go.
是，她怎么这样呢？
Yeah, but what is her problem?
丹尼斯，你在婚礼上把人甩了
Dennis, you left her at the altar...
怀着孕
when she was pregnant.
那都多少年的事儿了
But that was ages ago.
女人对这些事很在意
Well, women remember that stuff.
如果有什么我能帮忙的
Look, if there's anything else I can do to help...
尽管说
just let me know.
其实，我现在房租还差点
Well, actually, I am a little bit behind in my rent.
你有没有几百块？
I was wondering if you had a couple of hundred quid...
借我一下
I could maybe borrow.
我真喜欢你，真的
Oh, I love you. I really do.
我正需要笑声
I needed that actually.
真好，谢了，回见
That's great. Thank you. I'll see you later.
这个呢？
How about this one?
你肯定做不了
I bet you can't do it.
-我能做大声的 -来啊
- I can do a big one. - Go on.
看，看
Look, look, look, look, look.
这个好
That was a good one.
Yeah.
听我说
Listen.
抱歉昨天让你进了警察局
I'm really sorry about gettin' you arrested yesterday.
没关系
That's all right.
现在的大学
Most universities don't even look...
不注意这种记录
at things like that these days.
又来了
Hey, another one.
不知道你还有别的吗？
As far as I'm concerned, what else do you have?
-哦，她很好… -是啊，她
- Oh, she was great. - Yeah, well, she is...
Ooh!
-嘘 -抱歉
- Shh. - Sorry.
所以我想…
Um, but, yeah, so I think...
想听个秘密吗？
Do you want to hear a secret?
当然了
Absolutely.
我班上有个女生叫艾米丽
There's a girl in my class called Emily.
这应该不是秘密
Well, I'm sure that's not a secret.
老师知道
The teachers probably know about her.
她长得像雨蛙
She looks like a tree frog.
什么？
She what?
长得像雨蛙
She looks like a tree frog.
这么说人家可不好
That's not a very nice thing to say.
我喜欢雨蛙
I like tree frogs.
真的？
Oh, yeah?
胜过霍比特人？
More than hobbits?
这样啊
I see.
我觉得我们可以共度一生
I really feel we can make a life together.
“你觉得我们…”
"You really think we could..."
怎么好像威特的口气
Wait, that sounds like something Whit would say.
他确实说过
He did say it.
-跟谁？你妈？ -是
- What? To Mom? - Yes.
这个猪头
What a shithead.
爸！
Dad!
抱歉
Sorry.
我很高兴你长大了
Listen, I'm really glad you were such a big boy...
不计较…
about not gettin' into the whole...
《指环王》那事了
Lord of the Rings thing, you know?
没关系
That's OK.
威特买了明天前排的票
Whit's got us front row seats for tomorrow...
这回更好
so it's even better.
这个猪头
What a shithead.
爸！
Dad!
Well.
# Ah, yeah #
# Oh, yeah #
# I'm up on the eleventh floor #
# And I'm watchin' the cruisers below #
# He's down on the street #
# And he's tryin' hard to pull sister Flo #
# Oh, my heart's in the basement #
# My weekend's at an all-time low #
# 'Cause she's hopin' to score #
# So I can't see her letting him go #
# You betcha #
# Oh, yeah #
# Uh-huh #
要送的货在楼下
Deliveries are downstairs.
-不，我是… -沃特曼・休斯
- No, I'm... - Waterman Hughes.
-何事？ -早(法语)
- Yes? - Bonjour.
威特！
Whit!
多谢帮助
Thanks for your help.
伙计，有何贵干？
So, what brings you down here, man?
高档零售商的高级安全分析实践问题？
A little, uh, high-level security analysis...
啊？
in retail operation?
有什么事吗？我正要去健身房
Huh?
What can I do for you? I'm just on my way to the gym.
-我有堂单车课 -啊？
- I got a spin class. - Huh?
单车？就是自行车
Spinning? You know, spinning, bicycles?
哦，对
Oh, OK.
不，我想不如去喝一盅
No, I was thinking more along the lines of a pint.
喝一盅？哦，喝一盅
A pint? Oh, a pint.
Uh, wow.
我也想喝一盅
Um, I'd love a pint, actually...
但我得走了
but, uh, I really gotta hit this class.
我正在训练
I'm in training, you know?
你想来吗？
You wanna come along?
这健身方法不错
Uh, it's an amazing workout.
我想去，但我没服装
I... I'd love to, but I don't have any gear, so...
我借你
Well, I'll lend you some.
好
Great.
三、二、一！
Three, two, one!
我们正在爬坡！节奏上来！
We're climbing! Rhythm is up!
蹬！蹬！
Push! Push! Push! Push!
保持紧张！
Keep it up!
别偷懒！来！
No cheating! Let's go!
怎么样？没事吧？
How you doin' there? You all right?
你说什么？
What'd you say?
站起来！爬坡！
Out of the saddle! We're climbing!
用尽全力！
OK, let's make it really hard!
你想跟我谈什么？
So, what did you wanna talk to me about, man?
Ow!
杰克说你有《霍比特人》音乐剧的票
Jake said you had some tickets to the, uh...
to the hobbit musical.
是，我的朋友是投资人
Yeah, a friend of mine's an investor in the show.
他非送我不可？你说怪不怪？
He totally hooked me up. Can you believe that?
Hmm... um...
我在想…
I was just thinking, um...
你也不愿意坐足三小时看戏吧？
you know, you don't really wanna sit...
through a whole sort of three-hour kind of show, do you?
-所以 -其实…
- So... - Well, the thing is...
Oh.
杰克很迷这个
Jake's really kind of got his heart set on this, you know?
是啊
Yeah.
-来点粉？ -不用了
- Powder? - I'm fine.
确定？爽身的
You sure? Refreshing.
看得出来
I would imagine it is.
我就是想…你需要的话
I was just... I'm thinkin' maybe, you know, if you like...
我可以替你带杰克和丽碧去
then I could maybe take Jake and Libby for you, you know...
如果你愿意
if... if you want.
我知道你对那天票弄砸了很自责
Look, I know you must be kind of angry at yourself...
for messing up with the tickets the other night...
我希望能帮上你
and, uh, I'd like to help you.
真的，但是…
I really would, but, um...
问题是…
Well, the thing is...
我想跟杰克打成一片
I hope to be more and more a part of Jake's life, you know?
说实话，我还挺期待这场演出
And, uh, frankly, I'm kind of looking forward to this show.
可以让我和杰克互相进一步了解
Give Jake and I, a chance to get to know each other better.
我这话儿你了解了吧？
I mean, uh, you can see my point, can't you?
了解了
Yes, I can.
能问个问题吗？
So, can I ask you a question?
好
Sure.
你追到她为什么又放弃了？
You had her once, why did you ever let her go?
说实话，威特
To be honest, Whit...
下楼梯小心点儿
Whoa, whoa, whoa, I'd just be careful on the stairs here.
腿可能还硬着
Your legs might be a little rubbery.
我没事儿
I'm fine.
对不起，对不起
Oh, sorry. I'm sorry.
我没事儿…
I'm fine. I'm...
第一阶比较难下…
Yeah, the first step is often the, uh...
the difficult one.
我是丽碧，请留言
This is Libby. Leave me a message.
小丽，是我，给我回个电话
Hey, Lib, it's me. Can you give me a ring?
妈的！
Fuck!
你他娘是谁？
Who the hell are you?
别废话，开门
Just open the bloody door.
好
OK.
“丽碧美味糕点店”
-拿好，希望您喜欢 -谢谢
- There you go. Enjoy. - Thank you.
-四十八号 -有
- Forty-eight. - Yes.
好啊
Hello.
丹尼斯，我很忙
Dennis, I'm really busy.
能聊一下吗？
Can we talk?
不，不买就走吧
No, just buy something or go.
我要这个特色纸托蛋糕
OK. I, can I have one of your signature cupcakes, please?
能换成那个大的吗？
Actually, can I have this big one?
-丹尼斯 -那个也行…
- Dennis. - That one's fine...
我也喜欢
and, uh, I like that one, too.
-还要什么吗？ -要
- Anything else? - Um, yeah.
你看上威特哪点了？
What do you see in Whit?
-四十九号 -我是四十九号
- Uh, forty-nine. - Yes, I'm forty-nine.
-您要什么？ -不，我还没完
- What can I get for you? - No, I'm not done yet.
你完了
Yes, you are.
不好意思，你用完规定时间了
Sorry, I think you've used up your allotted time.
没有什么规定时间好不好？
You don't... You don't have allotted time, OK?
你在占用我的规定时间
Now you're using up my allotted time.
你没有规定时间，好吗？
You don't get allotted time, OK?
又不是竞猜节目
It's not like a game show, you know?
十五秒赢取面包圈什么的
You got, like, fifteen seconds to win a bun.
拜拜，丹尼斯
Goodbye, Dennis.
要什么？
Yes?
你好
Yes. Hello, yes.
你有那种小兔姜饼吗？
Um, do you have any of those little gingerbread rabbits?
没有，那些只在复活节卖
Oh, no. We just have those at Easter.
真抱歉
I'm so sorry.
Oh.
Hmm...
有别的动物形状的吗？
Do you have anything else shaped like an animal?
-打扰 -怎么？
- Excuse me. - What?
我还没付钱
I haven't paid for my order.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
借光
- Excuse me. - Yeah.
Excuse me.
抱歉
- Ow! - Sorry.
说真的，你看上他哪点？
Seriously, what do you see in him?
他是有钱
OK, he's well-off, all right?
长得不错
He's kind of... He's quite good-looking, you know?
那又怎样？
But I mean, so what?
你认为我是为了这个？
Is that what you think this is about?
傍个帅哥大款？
I just want some gorgeous sugar daddy.
帅倒不至于
I wouldn't say gorgeous.
我才不是看上这些
Well, that's not why I'm with him.
那你看上他什么？
Well, why are you with him?
给我一个理由
You know, give me one good reason.
一个？我可以举五十个
One? I could give you fifty.
-我是五十！ -等等
- I'm fifty! - Hang on a minute!
成熟，有责任感，体贴…
He's mature, responsible, considerate...
对杰克好
he's great with Jake.
-这才四个 -嗨
- That's only four. - Hello?
他是个好人，丹尼斯
You know what? He's a good man, Dennis.
他为慈善跑马拉松！真是的
You know, he runs marathons for charity, for Pete's sake.
那有什么！
Oh, big deal!
你能跑马拉松？
So you could run a marathon?
能给我来份果仁巧克力吗？
Could I have a chocolate brownie, please?
等会儿！
- Hang on! - Oh!
丽碧，我可以改
Look, Libby, I can change.
真的？那咱们结婚吧
Yeah? Well, great. Let's get married.
-真的？ -不！
- Really? - No!
咱们结过一次，记得吗？
We tried that once, remember?
你在婚礼上跑了，我怀着孩子
You left me at the altar, pregnant.
你个鸡鸡！
You cock!
丽碧，我可以改的，好吗？
Look, Libby, I can change, OK?
我已经变了，我可以证明
I have changed. I can prove it.
怎么证明？
How?
我要参加马拉松比赛
I'll tell you. I will run the marathon.
什么？
What?
威特跑的那个
The one that Whit's doin'...
我也跑，跑完全程
I'll run that, and I'll finish it.
算了吧，丹尼斯 你这辈子什么都没干完过
Come on, you've never finished...
anything in your entire life, Dennis.
你看…你…这
Oh, now, you... That's not...
-这个… -看，你连句话都说不全
- You know... - Look, You can't even finish a sentence.
别这样…
Don't... don't...
你这是在…那词儿怎么说？
You're just bein', you know, what's the word?
鸡鸡？
Cock?
我决定要鱼的形状的
I would settle for something shaped like a fish.
找卖鱼的去！
Well, go to the fishmonger!
我吃素的
I'm a vegetarian.
好好
OK. OK.
丹尼斯，请你走吧
Dennis, just please leave.
好，我走
OK. OK, I'll go.
但我会证明给你看的，丽碧
But I'm gonna prove this to you, Libby.
我也可以成熟，担待，体贴
I can be mature, considerate, and responsible.
丹尼斯？
- Oh! - Dennis?
什么，丽碧？
Yes, Libby?
两英镑，七十五分
It's two pounds, seventy-five.
哦，对了
Oh, yeah, right.
丹尼斯想跑就可以跑
Hey, if Dennis thinks he can run the race...
他能跑下来的
he can run the race.
-谢谢 -不可能
- Thank you. - There's no way
你跑马拉松？
you can run a marathon.
-怎么不能？ -因为你是个懒蛋
- Why not? - 'Cause you is a lazy bastard.
告诉你，我还参加单车课了呢
Hey, I'll have you know I go to spin classes.
去了一次
You went to one.
就弄得像约翰・韦恩一样 (其走路姿势独特)
Yeah, and now you walk like John Wayne.
嘿，这事对我很重要
Hey, this is important to me.
我说真的！
I mean it!
好了，我受够了做半吊子的男人
Look, I'm sick of being a nearly man, all right?
我受够了担惊受怕
I'm sick of being scared.
受够了每天的自责
I'm sick of the regret I feel every day...
因为我没种娶我爱的女人！
'cause I didn't have the guts to marry the woman I love!
明天六点这些统统结束！
All that ends tomorrow at 6 A.M.
# Ow! #
不错
Not bad.
嗨
Hi.
好点了？
Feel better?
好多了
Much.
单车课如何？
Oh, how was spin class?
很棒的健身方式
Uh, it was... It was an amazing workout.
是吗？
Is that right?
是的，而且我觉得…
Yeah. And I also thought it would be...
可以让我和威特互相了解
a good chance for me to get to know Whit...
a little bit better, so...
那我们可以一起吃顿饭
Well, maybe we should all go out for dinner then.
-真的？ -是啊
- You think? - Yeah.
然后一起去跳舞
And then we could go dancing.
-你开玩笑 -不，没开玩笑
- You're jokin'. - No, not at all.
之后我们可以一起回来
And then, afterwards, we could come back here...
来三人行
and have a threesome.
你开玩笑
Oh. You are joking.
当然！
Of course, I am.
丹尼斯，我不知道你想干什么 但不管是什么目的…
Look, Dennis, I don't know what's going on...
-我不希望你这样 -我…没有…
in that head of yours, but whatever it is...
- I don't like it. - I've... There's nothing...
-爸！ -嘿，伙计
- Daddy! - Hey, buddy.
-准备好上学了？ -恩
- You ready for school? - Yeah.
等下，等下
Wait up, wait up, wait up a sec.
咱们一起走好吗？
Can I walk with you guys?
好
OK.
-回头见 -好
- I'll see you later. - OK.
-拜 -拜拜
- Bye. - Bye-bye.
可以走了？
All right, you ready?
恩
Yeah.
威特，你来得很早啊？
So, Whit, you were, uh, 'round at Libby's pretty early, eh?
威特昨晚在这儿住的
Whit stayed over last night.
-哦？ -是的
- Oh? - Yes.
他们还玩跳床来着
They were jumping on the bed.
Wow.
知道吗，杰儿，我问朋友了
Hey, Jakey, guess what? Uh, I spoke to my friend...
他确实还有一张今晚的票
and he does have an extra ticket for the show tonight.
咱们带上艾米丽如何？
What do you say we, uh, ask Emily to come along?
好耶！
Yeah!
他告诉你艾米丽的事了？
- Yay. - What, he told you about Emily?
是呀
Oh, yeah.
听丽碧说你要跑马拉松？
Oh, and, uh...
Libby tells me that you decided to run the marathon?
是的
Yeah.
那太好了，真的
That's great, man. Seriously.
真的，很棒
Really, that's awesome.
谢谢
Thank you.
你怎么报上的？
How did you manage to get in?
什么意思？
What do you mean?
你不能上去就跑
Well, you can't just show up and run.
怎么？
Well, why not?
你要提前申请
You have to apply in advance.
提前多久？
Well, how far in advance?
三个月？
Uh, three months.
比赛还有多久？
And when is it again?
三个星期
Three weeks.
好
Right.
有时会为慈善事业的选手破例，但是…
They'll make exceptions sometimes...
if you're running for a charity, but, uh, you know...
每类慈善事业的名额有限
each charity is only allowed a certain amount of runners.
你不用担心我
No, you don't have to worry about me.
我能报上的
I'll get in.
好
All right.
你以前跑过马拉松？
You ever, uh, run a marathon before?
没有，怎么？
No. Why?
很累的
It's pretty gruelling.
是啊，所以才叫马拉松
Well, yeah, that's why they call it a marathon.
实际上叫马拉松…
Yeah, actually, technically, it's called a marathon...
是因为公元前490年的事件
because of the events of 490 B.C.
有一位希腊战士…
There was a Greek soldier...
-叫斐… -能不能打断一下
- named Phei... - Say, can I just...
什么
- stop you there? - Yeah.
没什么，就是打断
I've got have nothing to say. I just wanted to stop you there.
好
All right, all right.
你好，是猫儿保护联盟吗？
Hello. Is that the Cats Protection League?
你好，我想…
Hello. I was just...
参加这个月的马拉松比赛
I'm... I'm running a marathon next month...
不知能否代表你们出赛？
and I was wondering if I could possibly run on your behalf?
好，很好
Great. Yeah, yeah.
可以
OK. I see.
那服装多大？
How big is the costume?
好，回头打给你
OK. I'll call you back.
Ooh.
嗨
Hi.
-丹尼斯 -怎么？
- Dennis. - Oh, yes?
能不能别在顾客面前这样
Would you mind not doing that in front of the customers?
抱歉，我早上穿裤衩去跑步
Sorry. I went for a run this morning in my trunks...
可能起痱子了
and I think I've got a bit of a rash...
正好在…
you know, down there in the, uh...
-明白 -阴囊部位
- I understand. - Scrotal zone.
-我明白，丹尼斯 -好
- I understand, Dennis. - OK.
工作时间不要把手放在阴囊部位
Please, keep your hands out of the scrotal zone...
好
whilst you're at work.
Will do.
嘘
Shh.
丹尼斯！
Dennis!
对不起，我…
Sorry. I was, um...
我到位了
I was in the zone.
打扮成大脑？
So, um, I'd actually be dressed as a brain.
再联系好吗？
Um, can I call you back?
#你想得倒是轻松#
# Just 'cause you think it #
#哪有这种好事#
# It don't make it so #
#喝个烂醉如泥#
# Drive you to drink #
#结果还是做梦#
# Won't let you go #
#恋爱中的姑娘小伙#
# Plenty of girls and boys in love #
大哥呀！
Come on!
#姑娘小伙在恋爱中#
# Plenty of girls #
# And boys in love #
想喝杯茶吗，丹尼斯？
Would you like a cup of tea, Dennis?
就是这样
So that's it.
跑马拉松是我最后的机会
Running this marathon could be my last chance...
向丽碧证明我变了
to show Libby that I can change.
Mmm.
知道换我会怎么做吗？
You know what I would do if I were you?
怎么？
What?
找点皮疹膏
I would get some cream for that rash.
问你个事，丹尼斯
Let me ask you something, Dennis.
你为什么在婚礼上丢下怀孕的妻子？
Why did you leave your lady at the altar when she was pregnant?
不清楚，就是没准备好
I don't know. Just wasn't ready.
大米饭都熟了，朋友
The toothpaste was already out of the tube, my friend.
跟准备好有什么关系？
Being ready had nothing to do with it.
我害怕
I was scared.
Mmm.
这么说你是个懦夫
So, you are a coward.
我以为就喝茶随便聊聊
I thought we were just gonna have a cup of tea.
你认为你不够好
You did not think you were good enough.
对不对？
Am I right?
你想到妻子，害怕…
You thought of your lady, and you were terrified...
你无法给她应得的一切
you could not give her what she needed...
what she deserved.
我以前也有这个想法
I thought the same things...
跟古施达施迪达赫夫人结婚的时候
on the day I married Mrs Ghoshdashtidar.
愿她安息
May she rest.
你也是？
Did you?
是，但猜怎么着？
Yes. But guess what?
最后证明我足够好
It turned out I was good enough.
我努力做到够好
I made myself good enough.
你是做错了，丹尼斯
You did a stupid thing, Dennis.
但她爱过你，那毕竟是你赢来的
But she loved you once, and you must have earned that somehow.
是啊
Yeah.
你的婚姻幸福吗，古施达施迪达赫先生？
Did you have a good marriage, Mr Ghoshdashtidar?
Ah.
我记得那种合二为一的感觉…
I remember the feeling of being complete...
每天都像和最好的朋友一起度过…
of spending every day with my best friend...
而最幸福的…
but most of all...
是我记得所有的性交…
I remember all the fucking.
Mmm...
右舷转向三度，船长
Oh, three degrees starboard, skipper.
嘿，我是船长
Hey, I'm the captain.
兵变夺船！
Mutiny! Mutiny!
Whoa!
来啦，小伙子
Ahoy there, me lad.
-噢 -嘿，杰儿
- Oh! - Hey, Jakey.
抱歉迟到了，宝贝
Sorry, we're late, love.
威特知道要来这儿
Soon as Whit found out we we're meeting here...
非拿他的船来不可
he had to go get his vessel.
杰儿，拨这个开关
Jakey, here. Flip that switch.
不，是这个
No, not that one. That one.
哇！我能开吗？
Whoa! Can I steer it?
不行，但你可以看我开
No. But you can watch me steer it.
兵变
Mutiny.
能来下吗？
Hey. You wanna?
-他还乖吗？ -很乖
- Was he OK? - Yeah, he's fine.
我们玩得很好 要不是布莱船长出现的话
We had a really nice time until Captain Bligh turned up.
威特干什么都很认真
Whit just likes to take things very seriously.
要么投降，要么就尝尝女王陛下 皇家舰队齐射的怒火吧！
Prepare to be boarded, or feel the hot wrath...
of Her Majesty's royal fusillade!
等等，别碰那个
Wait, don't touch that. Wait.
我为什么不能开？
Why won't you let me steer it?
因为船是我的
Uh, because it's mine.
你还要跑马拉松？
So, you're still gonna run in this marathon?
当然，必须的
Yes, absolutely.
一定很好的
It's gonna be great.
你将看到全新的丹尼斯
You're gonna see a whole new Dennis.
好，我考虑过这件事
Right, well, I've been thinking about it...
我觉得，我不关心
and the thing is, I don't care.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
丹尼斯，你认为你会获得什么？
Dennis, what do you think you're going to achieve?
你真觉得跑上二十六里路
Do you honestly think that running 26 miles...
就洗心革面了？
is just gonna wipe the slate clean?
也许穿短裤跑可以
Well, you might change your mind when you see me...
in jogging shorts.
过几周威特要为我办生日宴会…
Look, Whit's having a birthday party...
你来的话，杰克会很高兴
for me in a couple of weeks...
and it would mean a lot to Jake if you came.
只为杰克？
To Jake?
Hey!
谁的船？
Hey, OK.
Whose boat is this?
Whose boat... is this?!
有人吗，这是谁的船？
Excuse me! Is... Is this your boat?!
-不可能！ -他是个废物
- No way! - He's toast.
坚持不下来的
He won't last.
来点比萨？丹尼斯？
Would you like some pizza, Dennis?
好，非常感谢
Oh. Yes, I would actually. Thank you very much.
过来
- Ow! - Come here.
你干什么，别打我
What are you doing that... Stop it.
你还跑吗？
Are you still gonna do this?
你还跑马拉松吗？
Are you still gonna run the marathon?
想跑
I want to, yes.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
怎么？
Why?
因为我把钱都压上了
Because I just bet them every penny I have.
什么？你压我了？
What? You bet on me?
丹尼斯，你是我最好的朋友
Dennis, you're my best friend.
我当然压你
I'm not gonna bet against you.
谢谢
Well, thank you.
赔率这么高
Not with these odds.
我跑不完怎么办？
Well, what if I don't finish?
文森特会杀了你
Vincent'll kill you.
你能跑完的
Oh, you'll finish.
你怎么这么确定？
How can you be so sure?
起来！起来！起来！
Get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up!
你是我的教练
So, you're gonna be my coach.
对
That's right.
你又来干嘛？
Why are you here?
我是助理教练
I'm the assistant coach.
你凭什么当助理教练？
Why do you get to be assistant coach?
凭这把平铲
Because I have this spatula.
Ow!
快，跑
Go on. Get running.
有什么特殊的技巧吗？
Wait. Isn't there some sort of special technique?
有，把一只脚放另一只前…
Yeah, you put one leg in front of the other...
快速反复交替
over and over again really fast.
你来干什么来着？
Why are you here again?
鞭策
- Ow! - Motivation.
# I said, yeah #
- # What they said # - # What they said #
膝盖抬高！
- # Oh, I said, yeah # - Lift your knees higher!
你这样跑不动的
- You're not gonna get... - # Yeah, yeah #
- anywhere like that! - # It's what they said #
- You've gotta slide more. - # What they said #
快，丹尼斯
- # Do you believe I would take something with me # - Come on, Dennis!
想尝尝我的平铲？
- You want to feel my spatula?! - # And give it #
不想
- No, I do not! - # To the police man? #
那就跑，像风一样！
- Then run! Run like the wind! - # I wouldn't do that #
我也挺累的
- # And if I do that # - This is harder...
- # I would say, "Sir" # - for me, you know?
# "Come on and put the charge on me" #
Ow!
# I wouldn't do that #
快，丹尼斯！ 快！
- # No, I wouldn't do that # - Come on, Dennis! Come on!
情况不错
- Lookin' good! Lookin' good! - # I'm not a fool to hurt myself #
保持住，丹尼斯
- Come on, Dennis. Keep up the pace. - # I was innocent #
等等，等等
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. - # Of what they done to me #
# They was wrong #
脚好像起泡了
I think I got a blister.
好
- # They were wrong # - OK.
轻点
Yeah, gently.
好
All right.
噢，好的
OK! Oh! All right.
-很糟吗？ -不，不糟
- Is it bad? - No, it's not that bad.
不，不糟
No. No. It's not.
好大
Ohh! Oh, that's big.
看看
Look at that thing.
就像子宫一样
It's like a womb.
别碰
Don't.
也许里面住着小人
Hey, maybe there's a little man in there...
长得和你一样，跑的比你快
who looks just like you, but he's really good at running.
你说什么呢？
What are you talking about?!
只是个念头
It's just a thought.
你来弄破
You're gonna have to pop it.
我不
No. No way.
我不挤别人的脓
Never pop another man's pustule.
那我来，给我针
Well, I'll do it then. Give me the needle.
这是能找到最小的
That's the closest I could get.
没事儿，消毒了
It's fine. I sterilized it.
用什么消的？
In what?
消毒了
It's sterilized.
好，来了
OK, OK. Here we go.
你能做到
Ooh, you're gonna get it.
忍住
Stick it in.
-扎！ -我不行
- Pop it! - I can't!
-为什么？ -我害怕
- Why not? - It's scary!
给我
Give it to me.
慢慢的！
Just do it slow!
-轻轻的，好吗？ -好
- Do it... Do it gently, OK? - Yeah.
-相信我 -数三个数，好吗？
- Trust me. - After three, OK?
-好 -一
- OK. - One.
插进去了！
It's in it!
拔出来！
Get it out!
快他娘拔出来！
Bloody take it out!
-别动！别动！ -拔！
- Hold still! Hold still! - Get it!
真抱歉
I'm so sorry.
尚无先例
That's never happened before.
Oh! Oh!
我是天主教徒
I'm Catholic.
这是我眼睛里进过的第二恶心的液体
That was the second most disgusting fluid...
I've ever had in my eye.
谁？
Who's that?
古先生
That's Mr G.
打扮像样点
Get something nice on, something respectable.
去哪儿？
Where we goin'?
每年都有近千人
Every year, literally hundreds of people...
受神经脑皮层损伤的折磨
are affected by acute neurocortical emphasitis...
又称哈布斯堡综合症
or Hapsburg Syndrome.
是的
I see.
这种病症有什么征兆？
And how does the condition manifest itself?
这种症状表现为…
The syndrome is characterized...
下肢瘫痪…
by a loss of lower body function...
间歇性失控狂怒骂人
sporadic and often violent outbursts of profanity.
以及常年胃肠胀气
And often chronic flatulence.
我们希望人们关注这种症状…
It's our aim to raise awareness of the condition...
并资助…
and, hopefully, some funds to give...
这些急需帮助的…
some much-needed support...
像古施达施迪达赫先生一样的人
to people such as Mr Ghoshdashtidar here.
Mmm...
-我们认为高施达施迪… -古施！
- Well, we think that Mr Goshdashti... - Ghosh!
-高施达施迪达赫… -古施！ 古施！
- Ghoshtashtidar... - Ghosh! Ghosh!
古施达施迪达赫的情况很严重
Ghoshtashtidar's condition is very, uh, serious...
我们可以认可，并很乐意…
and warrants support, and we'd be delighted...
让道尔参加比赛 以唤起人们对急性……
for Mr Doyle to run on behalf of acute neuro...
急性神经脑皮层损伤
Acute neurocortical emphasitis.
-又称… -哈布斯堡…
- Or, uh... - Hapsburg Syn...
综合症的关注，好的
Syndrome awareness. Yes.
好
OK.
只需要慈善注册编码
We'll just need the charity's registration number.
什么？
The what?
注册编码
The registration number.
糟到家了
Well, that couldn't have gone any worse.
Mmm.
小心！
- Look out! - Oh!
被轮椅砸了
Ohh!
Aw, hit by a wheelchair.
真对不起，真对不起
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
-疼 -上帝呀
- It stings. - Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
-疼 -别！别！
- It stings. - No, no, no, no!
丹尼斯，别动！
Dennis, don't touch him.
-你能站起来吗？ -不
- Can you stand? - Oh, no!
-你还好吗？ -不，我的腿断了
- Are you OK? - No. My leg's broken.
真对不起
We are so sorry.
你叫救护车
You... Call an ambulance!
怎么会这样
Oh, this can't be happening.
我还有三个星期就要跑马拉松了
I was supposed to be running the marathon in three weeks.
-真的？ -是
- Really? - Yeah.
很多人指望着我呢
There were so many people dependin' on me.
慈善受众？
Charity people?
是
- Hmm? - Yeah. God!
哪些慈善受众？
What charity people?
觉得怎样？
What do you think?
“勃起障碍”
Nice.
不错
戒烟帖？
Nicotine patch?
贴毕
Applied.
-厕所？ -大小皆空
- You been to the toilet? - One and two.
准备好了？
You ready?
好了
Ready.
一
One.
-一 -上去
Ow.
- Two. - Get up there.
# This is a jailbreak #
# This is a Thursday afternoon #
# But I didn't mean it #
- # I didn't mean it # - Ow!
# I'd never get that far #
# My baby, short breath wouldn't do #
# But you took it serious #
加注
- # Took it so serious # - Raise.
-不！ -不！
- No! - No!
一…二
One, two...
我再来一个！
One more! One more!
# Well, you accused me of wearing movies in my eyes #
# But I still love you #
# Of course, I love you #
# And so I countered #
# You do the same, my Annie I #
# You closed them so fast #
# And you closed them so tight #
-嗨，丹尼斯 -啊…
- Hi, Dennis. - Wha...
我今天看见你朋友戈登了
I saw your friend Gordon this morning.
他偷什么了我赔
I will replace anything he stole.
他告诉我打赌的事
He told me about his little bet.
是吗？
Oh, yeah.
-很刺激啊？ -是啊
- Yeah. Crazy, huh? - Yeah.
我也赌赌刺激一下
So I made a crazy little bet of my own.
跟谁赌？
Ooh. Who with?
你呀，傻瓜
With you, silly.
-咱俩没赌啊 -这就赌
- We haven't made a bet. - We're about to.
听我说
Here it is.
你跑完全程…
You finish the race...
我就免了你欠的房租
I'll forgive all the back rent you owe.
-我要是跑不完呢？ -要是你跑不完
- And if I don't? - If you don't finish...
就拿了包走人
you pack your bags and you leave.
你走了我再找些干净点的租户
You go, and I finally get some tidy tenants...
能及时付房租的
who pay their rent on time.
-说定了？ -没定
- Deal? - No deal.
嘿，你干什么… 给我
Hey, what are you... Hey, give me that.
-说定了？ -定了
- Deal? - Deal.
-玛雅，你要是想… -玛雅？
- Maya, if you think making... - Maya?
嘿，古施达施迪达赫先生
Hey. Hello, Mr Ghoshdashtidar.
怎么样？
How are you?
我有样东西给你
I've got something for you.
不是平铲吧？
Ooh. It's not the spatula, is it?
不
No.
Wow.
助你成为好人
To help you be a good man.
我…
I don't...
谢谢
Thank you.
Wow.
完美皮特，完美住所
Peter Perfect, a perfect palace.
等你喝醉了再承认不迟
Try saying that when you're smashed.
我会的
- I will. - # Lately #
# I been high-steppin' #
嗨，丹尼斯
# I've got a lover #
- # Who just gets it for real # - Hey. Hey, Dennis.
-嗨 -很高兴你能来
- Hey. - Glad you could make it.
-谢谢 -嗨
- Thank you. - Oh, hey.
哇，丽碧
Wow, Libby.
你看起来…
You look, um... wow.
谢谢
Thank you.
是啊，在这里…
I know, right? Never mind all this.
你就是最美的景色
I'll take the view I have right here.
Oh.
我是戈登，丽碧的表弟，你好
I'm Gordon, Libby's cousin. Hello.
戈登，我常听她提你
Gordon. Of course. I've heard a lot about you.
非常高兴认识你
Very nice to meet you.
-真的？ -是
- Really? - Yeah.
你不是说他是混蛋吗？
Oh. I thought you said he was an asshole.
-丹尼斯！ -戈登
- Dennis! - Gordon.
-怎么？ -没关系，小丽
- What? - It's OK, Lib.
丽碧，我送你的生日礼物
Libby, I got you a birthday present.
哦
Oh.
是盘CD
It's a CD.
希望没有重样，我没法退…
I hope you don't have it, 'cause I don't have a receipt...
因为不是买的…
and I didn't exactly get it in a shop.
那谢谢了
Well, thank you, I think.
卫生间在哪？
It's OK. Where's the toilet?
我领你去，你招待一下丹尼斯
I'll show you, and, uh, you can entertain Dennis.
好
OK.
只要他不介意跟混蛋在一起
That is if he doesn't mind hangin' out with an asshole.
他说着玩的，我没说你是混蛋
He was joking. I never said you were an asshole.
-你说了 -是，我说了
- Yeah, you did. - Yeah, I did.
威特不错啊
Whit seems nice.
是啊
Yeah, he is.
长得俊，绅士，有钱，工作稳定…
Good-looking, friendly, well-off, steady job...
对杰克好
good with Jake...
就像脱销了一般
just like you got him out of a catalogue.
怎么理解？
And what's your point?
我上次买了一双畅销鞋
I ordered a pair of shoes once from a catalogue.
上好的意大利软皮洛夫鞋
Gorgeous soft leather Italian loafers.
看着好极了，结果收到货
They looked amazing, but then they arrived...
穿上像踩地雷似的
and I put them on, and they hurt like fuck.
谢了，我记住了
Thanks. I'll bear that in mind.
Wow.
我在这儿洗个澡会不会很怪？
Hey, do you think it would be weird if I took a bath?
是很怪
Yeah, that would be weird.
-给 -谢了
- Hey. - Hey.
- Here you go. - Oh, thanks.
干杯
Cheers.
你觉得怎么样？
What do you think?
有人往你车上撒尿
I think I see a guy peeing on your car.
-什么？ -骗到你了
- What? - Got you.
哦，厉害
Oh, very good.
看到哪儿了吗？
Actually, you see that?
什么？
What?
那儿，圣・保罗大教堂
There. I'm talking about St. Paul's Cathedral.
-看见了？ -呃…
- You see it? - Uh-huh.
目前是我最喜欢的伦敦景点
Currently my favourite spot in London.
知道为什么吗？
You know why?
因为你在那里第一次…
Uh, is it because that's where you first realized...
发现自己很出色？
how amazing you are?
那里是马拉松的终点
It's the finish line for the marathon.
再有两天，我就会穿过那儿
Only two more days, and I get to cross it.
真等不及了
Can't wait.
我也是
Me, too.
成功跑完长跑是世上最棒的事
Greatest feeling in the world, finishing a distance race.
你肯定会跑得很开心
I think you're really gonna get a kick out of it.
你觉得我跑不完，是不？
You don't think I'm gonna finish, do you?
是的
No, I don't.
为什么？
Why not?
因为那很难，丹尼斯
'Cause it's really hard, Dennis.
需要一些…
Actually requires a couple of things...
抱歉，你没有的东西
that, uh, forgive me, but you don't seem to possess.
不好意思，我正好有一双很棒的跑鞋
I happen to have a very nice pair...
of running shoes now, thank you very much.
我是说方法和坚持
I'm talking about discipline and perseverance.
且不说别的
And all cute little comments aside...
赛程中总有那么一点…
there comes a point in every race...
可能是十五里，可能二十五
it could be the fifth mile, it could be the 25th...
你会撞上…
but, eventually, you're gonna hit...
赛手们说的那堵“墙”
what runners like to call "the wall."
到时候…
And when you do...
你会喘不上气，脑子一片空白 挪不动腿
you won't be able to breathe or think or even move.
只想放弃
All you're gonna wanna do is give up.
而我有强烈的预感…
And I have a very strong feeling...
你会放弃的，丹尼斯
that that's exactly what you're gonna do, Dennis.
这就是区别
See, that's the difference...
追上丽碧这样的女孩
between getting a girl like Libby...
和守住丽碧这样的女孩
and keeping a girl like Libby.
还需要别的吗？
You good? You need anything else?
-不，我很好 -好
- No, I'm good. - OK.
# Love is sweet, they say #
# Promises of tomorrow #
# But the tighter you grip, the faster you slip #
# This much I know #
# Lately, I want everything #
# Every star tied to a string #
# Coffee, tea, and in between #
# The sweetest smile I've ever seen #
# A different song in every room... #
-该死！抱歉，抱歉 -没事
- Oh, shit! Sorry. Sorry. - That's OK.
-不，没事 -真是的…
- No, it's OK. It's OK. - Oh, man. It's just...
只是汽水
It's just soda water, honestly.
那我不要揉你胸部了？
Should I not rub your boob, then?
-是啊 -抱歉
- Yeah. - OK. Sorry.
我可以再揉揉这个…
I can do the other one, you know?
得平等对待嘛…
'Cause I'm here, I might as well just even it out.
不好意思
Sorry.
怎么样，你高兴吗？
So, you havin' a... havin' a good time?
是的，谢谢
Yeah. Yes, I am, thank you.
你瘦了
You've lost weight.
是啊，一点点
Yeah, just a little bit.
是啊
Yeah.
锻炼嘛
You know, get on.
杰克在哪？我以为他也来的？
Where's Jake? I thought he was gonna be here.
不
Uh, no.
威特觉得找保姆陪他 我俩能好好过个生日
Whit thought that we'd have a better time...
if we got a sitter.
你觉得呢？
Oh. What did you think?
我该回去了
I should get back.
丽碧，我一直没感谢你
Libby, um, I never actually thanked you.
感谢我什么？
For what?
让我重新回到你的生活中
Well, for just sort of lettin' me back into your life.
杰克的生活
Jake's life.
你也知道
Yeah, well, you know.
你再也不理我也很正常
I mean, I-I wouldn't have been surprised...
if you just cut me off completely, you know?
我怎么没想到
Ugh, now you tell me.
我的意思是…
Well, no, I mean...
不，他需要爸爸
No, he needs his dad.
是啊
Yeah.
你说的对，我参加马拉松
You were right, you know, about me enterin' the marathon.
是为了…
It... You know, it was because I was...
挽回你
sort of trying to win you back kind of thing.
我一直希望咱们…
And I'd always kinda hoped that maybe, we'd, you know...
可以复合
get back together and that...
所以但我看到你和威特…
but, you know, when I saw you with Whit...
-丹尼斯 -我知道，我知道
- Dennis. - I know... I know... I know...
我知道这样说很虚伪
I know it's the height of hypocrisy, and I know...
我知道说了也不会改变什么
I know doin' this isn't gonna change anything...
或弥补什么…
or... or make anything better, but, um...
但我为你着想
I'd just... I'd settle for your respect.
希望你能微笑着
You know, I'd settle for you smiling...
回忆我们一起度过的日子
when you thought about the time that we had together...
不会觉得那段时光不值得
and not thinkin' it was a waste of time.
我想说的是
You know, I mean, I know...
我那天让你失望了，好吗？
I didn't do you any favours on that day, OK?
我错了，大错特错
I did a stupid, stupid thing.
但那是因为我觉得…
But it was only because I thought...
毁你一生不如毁你一天
spoiling your day was better than ruining your life.
你觉得有道理吗？
Does that make any sense?
你真是个傻瓜
You're such an idiot.
送你样东西
Hey, I got you something.
什么？
Oh, what is it?
你没有的东西
It's something I think you don't have.
靠得住的男朋友？
A history of reliable boyfriends?
不，只是…
No, it's... Well, it's only, you know...
-晚些打开 -好
- Open it later on. - OK.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
-谢谢 -不会
- Thank you. - No.
Oh.
-各位，我有话要说 -上帝
- Everyone, could I have your attention? - Oh, my God.
各位，请听我说
Hey. Everyone, your attention, please.
嗨
Everyone, hi.
感谢你们的到来
Thank you for coming.
-很高兴看到各位 -谢谢
- Really good to see you all. - Thank you.
大家都知道我们是来庆祝…
As you all know, we're here to celebrate...
伊丽莎白・奥利维亚・奥戴尔的生日
the birthday of one Elizabeth Olivia O'Dell.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
很多人知道我最爱跑步
As many of you know, uh, my passion in life is running.
再过几天
In fact, in a couple of days...
我将跑完另一场马拉松，谢谢各位
I'll be completing another marathon, thank you very much.
跑得好和爱情成功有共同之处
Uh, now, success in running requires a lot...
of the same things as success in love...
热情，决心…
passion, determination...
还有和丽碧相处很需要的…体力
and something I've needed a lot of with Libby, stamina.
真不会说话，是不？
That's just inappropriate, isn't it?
绕这么久，我想说的是…
The long-winded point I'm trying to make...
爱情和跑步都需要心
is that both love and running require heart...
而丽碧的心特别真
and Libby has... truly, has more heart...
胜过我见过所有的人
than any other person I've ever known.
生日快乐，宝贝
So happy birthday, sweetie.
谢谢！
Thank you all.
休闲鞋！
Oh, trainers!
不好意思，让我看一下好吗？
I'm sorry. Can I, uh, just see this for a second?
各位都知道
Now, what, um... As most of you know...
我通常都是一个人跑…
I usually run my races alone, but I thought...
不知道你可否考虑…
I was wondering if you would consider...
陪我跑下去…
becoming my partner?
天呢
Oh, my.
丽碧，你愿意嫁给我吗？
Libby, will you marry me?
不，不
No, no, no, no.
好，我愿意
OK. Yes.
-真的？ -是
- Yes? - Yeah.
真美
So beautiful.
Just beautiful.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢各位
Thank you, everybody.
太疯狂了
Crazy.
我错过什么了？
What'd I miss?
So...
你这该死的…毒药
You bloody... poison.
追死你追
All right. You can stick it up your ass...
你个美国王八蛋
you big American prick.
# Our love has changed #
他们决定了，我无所谓
- I don't mind they've decided. - # It's not the same #
# And the only way to say it #
# Is say it #
# It's better #
# I can't concede #
# This way I feel #
# For all the time we spend together #
# Forever just gets better #
# See, what I'm trying to say is #
# You make things better #
# And no matter what the day is #
# With you here, it's better #
# I'll stand by you #
# If you stand by me #
# I think it's time that I reveal it #
# 'Cause I believe it #
# It's better #
# See, what I'm tryin' to say is #
# You make things better #
丹尼斯！
Dennis!
怎么办，丹尼斯？
So what do you think we should do, Dennis?
我跟杰克解释了，但他很不高兴
Jake got really upset when I tried to explain it to him.
你能不能和他谈谈
So, I just wonder whether maybe you could talk to him today?
跟他说
You know, just... If he heard it from you...
你永远都是他父亲之类的？
that you're always gonna be his daddy, you know?
看来你不节食了
I take it the diet's off.
丹尼斯，你有没有听我说？
Dennis, are you even listening?
丹尼斯！
Dennis!
什么？你要我告诉杰克…
What? You want... You want me to tell Jake...
威特人多么好
what a... what a... what a perfect guy Whit is...
他完美的新生活多么完美？
and it's all gonna be really perfect...
in his new perfect life?
不，可以换个说法
No. Not necessarily in those words.
真不敢相信你要嫁给他
I cannot believe you're gonna marry this guy.
他把订婚戒指从鞋里拿出来
He pulled your engagement ring out of a shoe.
别这样，丹尼斯，只有你…
Please, Dennis, you're the only one...
能让杰克接受这件事
who can help Jake feel OK about this.
好，你想嫁给威特，没关系
Listen, if you wanna marry Whit, that's fine, OK?
这么大姑娘，可以犯错了
You're a big girl, and you can make your own mistakes, OK?
但不要到我这儿，毁了…
But don't come down here while I'm eating...
我的全英式加餐早茶
my full English breakfast with extra breakfast...
希望我为你做嫁衣，好吗？
and expect me to make things easier for you, OK?
能不能来点番茄酱？！
Can I please get some ketchup here?!
我不跑了
I'm not gonna run.
什么？！
What?!
我说我不跑了
I said I'm not running.
什么叫你不跑了？
What do you mean, you're not running?
就是不跑了，不跑那破马拉松了
I mean, I'm not running. I'm not running a stupid marathon.
为什么？因为丽碧又要结婚了？
Why? Because Libby's getting married again?
你想怎样？
What did you think?
她永远找不到比你强的人？
She... She's not gonna find anybody better than you?
那我来教教你
Well, let me be the first to tell you.
你不是什么好榜样
You know, you're not a tough act to follow.
怎么？你以为我自己不知道？
Oh, what? You think I don't know that?
我无所谓了！
I don't care any more!
-我怎么办？ -什么你怎么办？
- What about me? - What about you?
我钱都在这里呢！ 很多钱！
I've got money on this! A lot of money!
这跟我没关系！
That is not my problem!
住手！
Quit it!
我不是轻易放弃的人
I'm not the quitter.
-放开我！ -我耳朵！
- Let me go! - Ow, my ear!
放手！
- Let go! - Ow!
好，好！
Oh, OK! Oh, all right!
好了！都冷静一下！
Oh, enough! Just... Just stop for a minute!
# Every day, I love you less and less #
# I've got to get this feeling off my chest #
# The doctor says all I need's pills and rest #
# Since every day, I love you less and less #
# Unless, unless #
跑不跑？
- # I know, I feel it # - Are you gonna run?
不跑！
# In my bones # - No!
# I'm sick, I'm tired #
妈呀！
# Of staying in control #
- # Oh, yes, I feel I race upon a wheel # - Oh, God!
-好，好 -你跑不跑？
- OK, OK, OK, OK. - You'll run?
# Oh, yes, I'm stressed #
# I'm sorry I digressed #
# lmpressed, you're dressed to SOS #
# Oh-oh #
我的蛋蛋！
- My balls! - # And my parents love me #
# Oh-oh #
对，跑吧！
- # And my girlfriend loves me # - That's it! Run away!
你就会这个
That's what you always do!
跑吧！
Run away!
# Every day, I love you less and less #
嘿，这…
Hey, what the...
-好啊，丹尼斯 -你干什么？
- Hello, Dennis. - What are you doing?
戈登打电话了
Gordon called.
他说你不跑马拉松了
He tells me you're not running the marathon.
-是啊，但是… -但是什么？
- Yeah, but... - But, what?
你跑还是不跑？
Are you running or not?
-不，但是… -那就行了
- No, but... - So there you go.
-等等 -不好意思，丹尼斯
- Wait... - Sorry, Dennis.
赌有赌规，你得搬出去
A bet's a bet. You're out.
古施达施迪达赫先生？ 古施达施迪达赫先生！
Mr Ghoshdashtidar? Mr Ghoshdashtidar!
-你他娘是谁？ -嘿，你看…
- Who the hell are you? - Oh, please, look.
-我以为你是个好人，丹尼斯 -是…
- I thought you were a good man, Dennis. - Yeah...
虽然脑袋不太灵光，但没关系
A little screwed up here in the head, OK.
可玛雅说的对，你不好
But Maya was right about you. You are no good.
-听我… -总是跑…
- Look... - Always running away...
却从不往正道跑
never running in the right direction.
是，但是…
Yeah, but, oh...
我还给你买了新鞋，丹尼斯
I bought you new running shoes, Dennis.
卖货的说那是最好的鞋了
The man said they were the best you can buy.
-是，但是… -“但是，但是！”
- Yes, but... - "But, but, but!"
总是“但是！”总给自己开脱！
Always "but"! Always excuses with you!
总找借口，说不是你的错
Always some reason why it's not your fault!
告诉你，楼下的丹尼斯・道尔
I have news for you, Dennis Doyle from downstairs.
都是你的错！
It's all your fault!
-嗨 -嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
你要卖旧货？
You... You havin' a yard sale?
不，丽碧呢？
No. Where's Libby?
去接杰克了
Uh, she's pickin' up Jake.
我恐怕得先恭喜你
I suppose, uh, congratulations are in order.
噢，谢谢
Oh, yeah. Well, thank you.
勇者胜了
Best man won.
我倒没觉得这是竞争
Well, I wasn't really aware it was a contest.
丹尼斯！丹尼斯！ 杰克在你这儿？
Dennis! Dennis! Is Jake with you?
没有，怎么？
No, why? I...
他在家吗？威特
Well, is he here, Whit?
-你不是去接他吗？ -杰克！
- I thought you were picking him up. - Jake!
-丽碧？ -杰克！
- Libby? - Jake!
丽碧，怎么…
Libby, what is...
-你跟他说什么了？ -什么？
- What did you say to him?! - I... What are you...
我什么都没说，怎么了？
I didn't say anything. What do you mean?
他去艾米丽家，然后不知怎么
Well, he was at Emily's and something happened.
就跑出去了
He just ran out.
-什么？ -他跑了，明白吗？
- What? - He has run away, OK?
杰克跑了！
Jake ran away!
杰克！
Jake!
戈登！
Gordon!
-怎么？ -杰克跑了
- Yes? - Jake's run away.
-什么？ -他跑了！
- What? - He's run away!
我马上下来
All right. Well, wait a minute.
先冷静，想一想…
Just calm down. Think for a second.
他可能去哪儿？
Where would he go?
嘿，小鼻涕孩
Hiya, snot-face.
他没事
Yeah, he's fine.
我们过一个半小时就回去了
We'll be back in about a half an hour, I guess.
好
OK.
妈妈生气了？
Is she mad at me?
不，你没事她就放心了
No, no. She's just glad you're OK.
发生什么事了？
Do you wanna tell me what happened?
艾米丽不想做我的女朋友了
Emily doesn't wanna be my girlfriend any more.
为什么？
Why not?
有另一个男孩，罗伯特…
'Cause there's this other boy, Robert...
他有条马尾辫…
and he's got a ponytail...
她现在喜欢他了
and she likes him now.
她喜欢他就因为他有马尾辫？
What, she likes him because he's got a ponytail?
嗯
Uh-huh.
杰克恩贝
Jake 'n Bake...
等你大了就知道了…
as you get older, you're gonna realize...
有很多事非我们所愿
there are a lot of things that you don't like, OK?
比这更糟
Things much worse than this.
而那时我们不能逃跑
And when those things happen, you can't just run away.
为什么？
Why not?
因为那解决不了问题
Because it doesn't solve the problem.
虽然你跑开了
You know, when you start running...
问题依然在那儿
the problem's still there.
你要直面它，想出办法
You've got to stick at it, and then figure out a way...
解决它，即便这很难
to solve the problem, even if it's really, really hard.
你就是这么做的吗？爸
Is that what you do, Dad?
爸？
Dad?
丹尼斯！
Dennis!
戈登！
Gordon!
-找到他了？ -是的
- Found him? - Yes.
好，你不能住这儿
Good. You can't stay here.
戈登！
Gordon!
怎么？！
What?!
我跑
I'm running.
那么上来吧
Well, come on up then.
真舒服，哪儿弄来的？
Wow, these are great. Where'd you get 'em?
-威特那儿 -谢谢
- Whit's place. - Thanks.
秘诀就是…
See, the trick is...
在赛前装一肚子碳水化合物
you got to load up on carbs the night before the race.
这是我在《时尚・Cosmo》上看的
I read it in Cosmo.
腿怎么样？紧不？
How are the legs? Not too tight?
不，挺好的
No. No, they're fine.
所有的都准备好了吗？
Have you got everything you need?
鞋，短裤，鸡鸡衫儿
You know, your shoes, your shorts, penis t-shirt?
是的
- Yes. - Oh.
现在没兴趣
I'm not really in the mood.
-这是抹乳头上的 -什么？
- It's for your nipples. - What?
二十六里跑下来 你的乳头将和衬衫产生无数次摩擦
You run a 26-mile race, a lot of friction...
is generated from your shirt to your nipples.
而马拉松之大患，即乳头发炎
And the last thing you want during a marathon...
-《时尚・Cosmo》？ -是的
is nipple chafing.
我可不往乳头上抹那玩意
- Cosmo? - Yeah.
这个也不吃了，我睡觉就好了
I'm not puttin' that on my nipples, OK?
And I'm not gonna eat this. Let's just go to sleep.
那么我来帮你铺床
Well, at least, let me make your bed for you.
还需要别的吗？
Anything else?
有枕头吗？
Have you got a pillow?
-没有 -那没了
- No. - Well, then I guess I'm fine.
明天要几点起床？
Hey, what time do you have to be up tomorrow?
闹钟定到七点吧
Well, we should set the alarm for about seven o'clock.
-我没闹钟 -为什么？
- I don't have an alarm clock. - Why not?
我哪儿也不用去
I never need to be anywhere.
比赛九点开始
The race starts at 9.00, OK?
我们至少八点前出发，好吗？
So we should leave here no later than 8.00, OK?
好
OK.
晚安
Night.
爱你呦
Love you.
在清晨向您问好
A very good morning to you.
伦敦美好的天气迎来了 首届年度耐克环河赛
It's a beautiful day here in London...
for the first annual Nike River Run.
现场的观众非常热情
We've had a very warm welcome from the crowd...
今天的天气也极适宜于本次比赛 丹妮斯
and we've got perfect conditions for this race, Denise.
是啊
We certainly have.
环绕着泰晤士河的这廿六点二英里
26.2 miles along the River Thames...
吸引了世界各地的一万名长跑爱好者
10,000 runners from all over the globe...
并使很多人有机会 为慈善事业筹集资金
and an amazing way for many of these folks...
to raise money for so many worthwhile charities.
可以看到，赛会人员…
And as we can see, race officials...
已经在起点忙碌起来 迎接将在一小时内开始的比赛
are already busy at the starting line...
with the start less than an hour away.
出租车！
- Taxi! - # Keep on runnin' #
Taxi!
出租车！
- # Keep on hidin' # - Taxi!
等等！
Wait!
- Wait! - # One fine day #
# I'm gonna be the one #
# To make you understand #
比赛线路极佳
- It's a wonderful course. - # Oh, yeah #
他们将环绕泰晤士河…
- They'll wind around the Thames... - # I'm gonna be your man #
穿过五座桥梁，包括欧斯尼桥…
They'll cross over five bridges, including Osney Bridge...
艾尔伯特桥，千禧桥
Albert Bridge, and the Millennium Bridge.
按自己的节奏跑，好吗？
OK, OK. So go at your own pace today, all right?
-稳扎稳打 -好，稳扎稳打
- Slow and steady. - OK. Slow and steady.
此外冠军的有力争夺者还包括…
Yeah, they're challenging the leaders we have here.
来自日本的日吉清水
One from Japan, Hiyusha Shinuzu...
当然，还有住荣山手
and, of course, up there also, is Sumi Yamata.
小心！
Watch it!
白痴！
- Idiot! - # Keep on runnin' #
倒回去！
- # Runnin' from # - The other way! Go back!
不回去！
- # My heart # - No, we're not goin' back!
另外还应关注肯尼亚的选手们
Amongst the names we should keep an eye on...
实力不容小觑的威尔森・迪泰 科林顿・戴瓦
are the men from Kenya.
Always so strong, Wilson Deetay and Collington Degwa...
是第一集团的常客
they always can be found at front of the pack.
只能载到这儿了，伙计
This is as far as I can get, mate.
你得载我到起点
But I need to get to the start of the race.
过了桥就是 请付十五磅，伙计
Well, it's just over the bridge. That's fifteen quid, mate.
你有钱吗？
Have you got any money?
师傅，钱有点小问题
Sir, we have a slight liquidity problem.
可惜了
That is a shame.
不，等等
Uh, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
看这是19…
Look, look. This is a 19...
40年的劳力士520蚝式恒动泡泡背表
...40 Rolex 520 Perpetual Oyster with a bubble back.
这可真不赖
That's not too shabby.
戈登，你不能给他…
Gordon, you can't possibly give him...
算是投资了
Hey, it's an investment.
戈登，谢谢
Gordon, thank you.
那一会儿见了
I'll see you later then.
# Keep on runnin' #
祝你好运！
Hey, good luck!
对于运动员们来说 今天的比赛从凌晨就已开始
Now, typically, the day would have started...
at the crack of dawn for most of these runners.
吃过了精心配制的早餐
They had a balanced breakfast...
做好了身体和精神上的充分准备
precise physical and mental preparation.
在这样的比赛中 把希望完全寄托于偶然的人
On a day like today, to leave anything to chance...
不是极其幼稚
you'd either have to be extremely naive...
就是纯粹的傻瓜
or a complete idiot.
# Everyone is talkin' about me #
这儿，往我这儿
Over here. To me, to me.
对，小心
That's it. Be careful.
那是古董
That's an antique.
-开始了吗 -还没有
- Did it start? Did it start? - Not yet.
-打开 -好啦
- Turn it on. - Here we go.
这些天来我们很高兴地看到 选手的背景混杂
What do we love about these days...
is the sheer mix of competitors.
模样身材个个不同
They come in all shapes and sizes...
从那边精英到…怎么说呢
from the elite over there to the... how should we put it...
不很精英的
not so elite.
是丹尼斯！
That's Dennis!
看这伸展运动
Look at that stretch. Look at that.
全注加倍？
Double or nothing?
好
Yeah, right.
比赛即将开始，作为赛前惯例 选手们应该热身了
Just a few minutes to go now. The warm-ups should be complete.
It's time, if you have one, for that pre-race ritual.
你真来了
Well, well, well. You made it, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
我来祝你好运
Just wanna wish you luck out there.
你也是，你乳头如何？
You, too. How are your nipples?
很好
Great.
-土司来了 -比赛即将开始，赛会人员…
- More toast. - Only a few moments...
你希望谁赢？爸爸还是威特？
to go now, and the officials are...
Who do you want to win, Daddy or Whit?
-你希望谁赢？ -当然是爸爸
- Who do you wanna win? - Daddy, of course.
-如果是业余的选手 -你呢？
- If you're one of the fun runners... - What about you?
-跑完全程就是胜利 -吃土司
- It's just about completing the course. - Eat your toast.
参赛选手的队伍蔚为壮观
And what a great turnout we've got here today.
为什么总是我扮乌龟？
Why am I always the tortoise?
愿赌服输
A bet's a bet.
借过…
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
抱歉
- Pardon me. - All right.
丹尼斯，真得承认…
Well, Dennis, I gotta admit...
我没想到你能走这么远
I didn't think you'd make it this far.
我是说…
I mean, uh...
你的过往战绩实在不敢恭维…
you don't exactly have the best, uh, track record...
那是过去，现在这是开始
now, do you?
Yeah, well that was then, and this is now.
不，丹尼斯
No, Dennis.
这是开始
This is now.
好
All right.
不用感觉你非得跟上我
Don't feel you have to keep up with me.
Well, don't feel you have to keep up with me.
好啊，要的就是这个劲儿
Oh, yeah, that's the spirit.
他们出发了，克里斯
And they're off, Chris.
又一次盛大的马拉松…
Yet another great marathon...
在伦敦开跑
getting under way here in London.
运动员在拥挤的伦敦街道上 跑上廿六点二里…
And having these great runners go 26.2 miles...
of crowded London streets...
你昨天对杰克说的很好
That was great, what you did with Jake yesterday, by the way.
谢谢
Thanks.
丽碧也很感激你
I know Libby really appreciated it, too.
那我很高兴
Oh, I'm glad.
她太感激了
In fact, she was so appreciative...
所以我们在床上小跳了一下
we had a nice little jump on the bed.
-什么？ -回见了
- What? - Have a good race.
这还不够吗？
Isn't it enough?
什么？
What?
你得到她了？还不够吗？
You got the girl, all right? Isn't it enough?
我只是觉得你应该明白…
I just think it's high time you realize...
你们已经结束了
that it's over, sir.
否则等我们搬去芝加哥 你会很难过
Otherwise, it's gonna be very tough for you...
- when we move to Chicago. - What?
什么？
You better slow down there, chief.
最好悠着点，哥们
你还差得远呢
You got a long way to go.
你也是
- Yeah, well, so have you. - Oh, yeah!
好啊
Yes, I like it.
我喜欢你这劲头
Run, fat boy, run!
跑吧，胖墩，快跑！
我能减肥
I can lose weight...
但你永远是个混蛋
but you'll always be an asshole.
-肯尼亚选手依然优势明显，丹妮斯 -看啊
Now, once again, it's still being dominated...
选手们正跑过河岸
- by the Kenyans, Denise. - Look at that.
The runners are making their way along the embankment.
多么美丽的…
What a beautiful view of the...
领先集团的选手们
So, here we are among the leaders of the moment.
在开局阶段步履轻松
The pace is relatively relaxed for the opening miles.
似乎有些太轻松了，克里斯
Maybe a little too relaxed, Chris.
有几位业余选手赶了上来
It looks like we've got a couple of amateurs...
coming up from the back.
妈！
Mom!
这两位男士怎么开心怎么跑
It looks like these two boys...
are running a race of their own here today.
在职业选手中掀起了一阵波澜
In fact, they're causing quite a stir...
这种场面出现在开局阶段 实在出乎意料
among the serious runners.
Not something you'd really expect...
at this stage in the race.
抱歉
Oh. Sorry, sir.
有人倒下了
There's a man down.
抱歉
Sorry.
注意力集中在这两位运动员身上
All eyes right now are on these two runners.
不，不，你在干什么？
No, no, no, no, no. What are you doing?
-我们将尽快带来相关报道 -慢点
- We hope to bring you that information quickly. - Slow down.
不过挺上镜的
But he looks good, doesn't he?
-是啊 -是啊
- Oh, yeah. - Oh, yeah.
…创造新的世界纪录
...setting a new world record.
你想证明什么？
What are you trying to prove?
她不爱你了
She doesn't love you any more, man.
我不是为丽碧而跑
I'm not doing this for Libby.
算了吧
Yeah, right.
你真可笑
You're ridiculous, dude.
怎么，威特，跟不上了？
What's the matter, Whit, can't keep up?
Oh!
爸爸！
Daddy!
丹尼斯！不，威特！
Dennis! I mean, Whit!
看起来很严重
It does look very serious.
我们将带来详细消息
We're getting some more information...
别起来！别起来！
Stay down! Stay down!
你干什么去？
Where do you think you're going?
-我得去帮助丹尼斯 -为什么？
- I have to go help Dennis. - Why?
因为我是助理教练
Because I am the assistant coach.
好耶！
Yes!
他在十里标记处一马当先
He now leads at the ten-mile mark.
看起来伤得很重
And that looks really painful.
恐怕他比赛将在利兹医院结束了
Looks like this runner's race day...
will be ending at a Leeds hospital.
真是可惜…
Yeah, absolutely tragic...
妈，想想办法！
Mom, do something!
-没错，让我们关注… -走
- We certainly do. Let's get back... - Come on.
女子组的领先选手
To the leaders in the female race.
妈的
Shit.
Huh?
戈登，我替大家说…
Gordon, I think I speak for everyone here...
还钱
when I say, "Give me my money."
五千块
Five grand, please.
钱的事是这样的
OK, here's the thing about the money...
说起来好笑
and, actually, it's kind of funny.
…我没有
Uh... I don't have it.
容我们出去谈下
Would you excuse us a moment?
我找一位病人，丹尼斯・道尔
Hi. I'm looking for a patient, Dennis Doyle.
你是家人嘛？
Are you family?
-是 -道尔？
- Yeah. - Doyle?
是的，丹尼斯・道尔
Yes, Dennis Doyle.
抱歉，没有这个人
Oh, I'm sorry, we don't seem to have anyone...
registered by that name.
你确定？他参加了马拉松
Are you sure? He's a runner in the marathon.
哦，那位运动员，有
Oh, the runner. Oh, yeah.
他刚到
Well, he's just arrived.
-丽碧？ -威特？
- Libby? - Whit?
你怎么知道我在这儿？
How'd you know I was here?
你怎么在这儿？
What are you doing here?
宝贝，那个疯子绊我
Honey, that psychopath tripped me.
把我绊倒，我的韧带可能伤了
He tripped me. I think I have ligament damage.
几位，我们能不能…
Guys, can we... Can we just...
伙计…我是病人啊
Fellas, can we... Look, I'm a patient, please.
再…来找我！
Just one... Find me!
慢点！
Easy, easy! Ow!
文森特，我刚才说没钱
Vince, look, when I said I didn't have the money...
是指没带在身上
I meant I didn't have the money here.
-我能还 -你一定会还
- I can pay. - Oh, you're gonna pay.
不，等等…文森特
No, wait. Look... Vincent.
干嘛？
Wait... Wait... What?
等下！
Wait. Wait a tick.
没这么快结束，伙计
Not so bloody fast, mate.
你他娘是谁？
Who the hell are you?
多亏你了，古先生！
Thanks a lot, Mr G!
你那朋友很够意思
Your friend is a man of honour.
什么，文森特吗
What, Vincent?
对，他说等回来再收拾你
Yes, he said he's going to kick shit out of you later instead.
真奇怪
I don't understand.
电视上说他送到这儿了
On the TV, they said he was being brought here.
稍等
One second.
我可以告他
I could sue him. You know that, right?
我可以告他…
I could sue him for everything he has...
但我真拿…
but, you know, seriously, what am I gonna do...
这个穷得只剩披萨盒 反基督的家伙没办法
with some pizza boxes and a Judas Priest t-shirt?
宝贝，那肯定是意外
Honey, I'm sure it was an accident.
你没在现场
Well, you weren't there, OK?
你没看到，他好像疯了
You didn't see it. He was wild-eyed, all right?
嘴角冒出白沫
He was frothing at the mouth at one point.
我就像跟疯狗跑马拉松一样
It was like running a marathon with Cujo, OK?
杰克，伙计，我来控制床好吗？
Jake, buddy, can I control the bed, please?
不行，但你可以看我控制
No, but you can watch me control it.
丽碧？你在哪儿？
Libby? Where are you?
-医院 -你和他在一起？
- The hospital. - Are you with him?
不，他没在这儿
No, he's not here.
什么叫没在这哪儿？
Well, what do you mean he's not there?
就是没在这儿
I mean, he's not here.
那他到底在哪儿？
Well, where the hell is he then?
知道了，还没结束呢
All right. It's still... It's on.
比赛还没结束
The race is still on.
你居然放戈登走，文森特
I can't believe you let Gordon go, Vincent.
-但他说他会付的… -回到报道当中
- Yeah, but he said he was gonna pay us... - Back to the story.
-对吗，文森特？ -第一段画面…
- Right, Vincent? - The first images are coming in...
-似乎拍自手机 -文森特？
- from what looks like a camera phone... - Vincent?
-文森特？ -画面上是一位孤独，神秘的运动员
- Vincent? - Showing a lone, mysterious runner.
他好像伤得很严重
Uh, he's looking very badly injured, I must say...
他使干道的交通…
and he's also causing some major traffic...
-出租 -是啊，是劳力士
- Cab. - Yeah, it's a Rolex.
我不会卖的，这就是传家宝了
I'm not gonna sell it. It's a family heirloom now.
干什么！
What!
等等！你们干什么？！
Wait! What are you doing?!
-上车！ -怎么能随便抢出租呢！
- Step on it! - You can't just take a man's cab!
知道啦！
All right!
好啊…
Hello, there...
楼下的丹尼斯・道尔！
Dennis Doyle from downstairs!
你他娘是谁？
Who the hell are you?
美人儿，加油！
You beauty, come on!
伦敦市落入余辉之中
And as the sun sets over London...
而我们依然在调查…
we're still looking into the identity...
这位神秘运动员的身份
of that mysterious runner.
加油，丹尼斯，你可以的！加油！
Come on, Dennis, you can do it! Come on!
目前唯一能确认的…
The only concrete thing we do know...
是他为勃起障碍而跑
is that he's running for erectile dysfunction.
好消息，布鲁姆先生
Good news, Mr Bloom.
韧带没有撕裂
No rupture, no ligament damage.
太好了
Oh, that's great.
杰克，不要闹了
Jake, please?
其实根本没什么伤
In fact, there's no real damage anywhere.
你确定吗，医生？
Are you sure, doctor?
杰克，别闹了
Jake, please.
这好像是…
It's, uh, like, uh...
你们运动员怎么说来着？
What is it you runners say?
撞到墙了
You hit the wall.
不不，那不可能
No, no, that... That's not possi...
妈的，能不能别弄床了，你个小兔崽子
God damn it, will you stop...
messin' around with the bed, you little shit?!
上帝呀
God.
晚上好，体育方面的最新消息
Good evening. It's time for a sports update.
首先是耐克环河赛
Top story, the Nike River Run.
稍后是对冠军的访谈…
We'll be chatting to the winner a little bit later on...
因为有无数的电子邮件和来电
but first, we've had thousands of e-mails and calls...
询问神秘运动员的消息
about our mystery runner.
而我们的报道小组…
Well, I can tell you now, our TV crew...
已经联系上了他
has just caught up with him.
借光，借光
Excuse me. Sorry.
能不能慢点走？
Will you slow down, please?
饿不饿？去吃点东西？
You hungry? You wanna get a bite?
停车！停车！
Stop! Stop!
下车
Everyone out. Get out.
-快！ -来了！
- Come on! - I'm goin'!
走开！
Hey!
Just go away!
-谁绊他一下 -走开！
- Somebody trip him. - Go away!
把他撞到
Knock him over.
不行，无效，违规
No, invalid. Off-side.
别碰他！离他远点！
- Oh! - Leave him alone! Get off him!
要不现在陪钱！
I want my money now!
别听他们的，丹尼斯！
Don't listen to them, Dennis!
你是胜利者！
You are a winner!
要不现在赔钱！
I want my money now!
别扔了！我有头盔！
Stop it! I'm wearing helmet!
离远点！
Clear off!
所谓“长跑运动员的孤独”
"The loneliness of the long-distance runner"...
正是丹尼斯・道尔的真实写照
a phrase epitomized by this man, Dennis Doyle.
他拖着重伤的脚踝跑完了之前的十一英里
For the last eleven miles, he's been running...
on what appears to be a severely sprained ankle.
真是对人类精神力量的伟大见证
What a testament to the power of the human spirit.
道尔先生，你现在感觉如何？
Mr Doyle, how do you feel?
你他妈觉得我感觉如何？
How the fuck do you think I feel?
多么发人深省
What an inspiration.
我们将继续为您带来最新报道
We'll keep you updated as this story progresses.
-别他娘挡路！ -抱歉
- Get out of the bloody way! - Sorry.
-真是值得纪念的一天 -丽碧丽碧，我很抱歉
- Well, what a remarkable day... - Libby. Libby, I'm sorry...
-这次泰晤士马拉松… -好吗？我失控了，我…
- we've had at the marathon on the Thames... - all right? I lost it. I...
-比赛的看点… -我昏头了
- with an event dominated as ever... - I wasn't thinking.
-在于观众和业余选手 -我很抱歉
- By the crowds and the fun runners... - I'm sorry.
-宝贝，能不能就… -但其中特别引人注目的…
- Honey, can we just... - but particularly by
-杰克，伙计 -是其中一人
- Jake, buddy... - one man.
我们要谈话，电视小点声，好吗？
Would you mind just giving us...
a little peace with the TV, please?
-谢谢 -加油，丹尼斯！
- Thank you. - Go on, Dennis!
整个伦敦…
The whole of London...
宝贝，我们能不能谈谈？
Honey, can we just talk about this, please?
“我们爱丹尼斯”
-抬头！ -坚持住，伙计！
- Chin up! - Keep it up, mate!
您认识道尔先生吗？
Do you know, Mr Doyle, sir?
我是他的助理教练
Oh.
I'm the assistant coach.
真的？你是？
Oh. Oh, really. What's your name?
-古施达施迪达赫 -高施…
- Uh, Mr Ghoshdashtidar. - Gosh...
-古施… -格施…
- Ghosh... - Gah...
叫我约翰就好了
OK, just call me John.
是我发掘了他
It was me who discovered his potential.
我喘不上气了
I can't breathe.
头要炸了
My head's gonna explode.
他跑不完了
He's not gonna make it.
我得停下了
I... I have to stop.
-我得停下了 -不
- I have to stop this. - No.
-对不起 -不，你不能，这是干什么？
- I'm sorry. - No, you can't. What are you doing?
你不能停，就快到了
You can't stop. You're nearly there.
真的？还有多远？
What? How much further?
只有短短的…九英里了
Lt... It's a little, tiny... Nine miles.
好，好
OK. OK.
不
Oh, no.
怎么？
What?
他撞上了
He's hit it.
宝贝，该睡觉了
OK, baby, let's get you to bed.
杰儿
Jakey.
-…观众和业余的选手 -丹尼斯
...by the crowds and the fun runners. - Dennis.
-刚打开电视机的朋友 -丹尼斯？
- For those of you just joining us... - Dennis?
丹尼斯・道尔，这位服装店的保安…
It looks like Dennis Doyle, a clothing store security guard...
已经跑了十小时四十五分钟…
running for the last ten and three quarter hours...
依靠着一条腿…
on basically one leg...
不跑完不休…
is refusing to rest until this race is run.
令人难以置信！
Unbelievable!
你这辈子什么都没干完过，丹尼斯
You've never finished anything in your entire life, Dennis.
你会放弃的
All you're gonna wanna do is give up.
我可不是轻易放弃的人！
I'm not the quitter!
你一定会放弃的，丹尼斯
That's exactly what you're gonna do, Dennis.
好，逃吧！逃吧！
Go on, run away! Run away!
你只会逃！
That's what you always do!
丹尼斯！
Dennis!
丹尼斯？
Dennis?
真不敢相信
Oh, I don't believe this.
好，伙计，好！
Yeah, boy, yes!
他在继续前进！
He's still going!
加油，你这美人！
Go on, you beautiful man!
请原谅，女士们先生们…
Apologies there, ladies and gentlemen, uh...
但在这样激动人心的情景面前 很难保持冷静
but it's, uh, really rather hard not to get caught up...
in the drama of it all.
我们再来看一下丹尼斯脚踝受伤的过程
Now let's take one more look at how Dennis broke that ankle.
就是这个
And here it is.
看起来与道尔先生身边的选手有关
It appears that the runner there...
next to Mr Doyle is involved in some way.
让我们再来看一下…没错
In fact, if we look at it again here... yes!
是他故意绊的！
He deliberately trips him!
王八蛋！
Bastard!
再次请您原谅…
Apologies again, uh...
那不…不是那样的
That didn't... That's not what happened.
那…不是那样
That is... That... That didn't happen.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我也不相信
I don't believe it, either.
我也弄糊涂了
I don't understand that.
那是怎么回事？
What is that?
宝贝，宝贝
Honey. Honey...
从那角度看起来是，但是… 是他绊我
That angle makes it look, but... He tripped me.
他绊我！是的，是他！
He tripped me! Yes, he did!
-加油，丹尼斯！ -是他！丹尼斯！
- Go, Dennis! - It's him! Dennis!
加油，丹尼斯！
Go, Dennis!
真是的
I can't believe this.
真的，宝贝
Come on, honey.
好像我会做那种事似的
Please, like I'm gonna do that.
你不是开玩笑吧？
What are you... Are you kidding me?
宝贝
Honey.
好吧，听我说，我是…
All right, look, I'm just... I'm not...
身不由己，好吗？
I'm not myself, OK?
我身不由己好长时间了
I haven't been myself for a long time.
我的工作一直…
Work has not been...
这…
It's, uh...
就是这个城市的原因
It's just this city, you know?
我在这里很难受
It's just... It's really hard here for me.
这里人礼貌得过分
You know, everyone's so polite here...
还有这里的饭菜，还有车…
and it's like the food and the... and the... and the ca...
我不知道我怎么了
I just don't... I don't know what happened to me.
我不知道怎么…是这个地方的原因
I don't know what... It's just this place.
怪这个地方
It's this place, you know?
等我们…等我们搬走就好了
And if we... I just know it's gonna be better once we move.
-搬走？ -到芝加哥
- Move? - To Chicago.
什么？
What?
太早了？
Too soon?
-走，杰克 -丽碧…
Oh!
- Come on, Jake. - Libby, wh...
你去哪儿？你去哪儿？
Where you goin'? Where you goin'?
不会吧，找丹尼斯？
Oh, you got to be kidding me. Dennis?
这不可能
You can't be serious.
这家伙在婚礼上把怀孕的你丢下
The guy left you at the altar pregnant.
谁都有缺点
Nobody's perfect.
丽碧
Libby.
丽碧！
Libby! I...
真是个猪头
What a shithead.
杰克
Jake.
我知道你很难受
Hey. I know you feel bad.
也很痛…
I know you're in incredible pain...
但你马上就能让我去度假啦
but you are so close to me going on holiday.
走
Come on.
丹尼斯！丹尼斯！丹尼斯！
Dennis! Dennis! Dennis!
距离终点圣・保罗大教堂如此之近 着实令人激动
As we draw tantalizingly close to the finish line...
here at St. Paul's Cathedral...
可以说 我和我的摄影师度过了漫长的一天
it's safe to say, it's been a very long day...
for myself and my cameraman.
而在家观看的您，也度过了漫长的一天
It's been a very long day for you watching at home...
但对丹尼斯・道尔来说
but for Dennis Doyle...
这是他一生中最长的一天
it's been the single longest day of his life.
加油，丹尼斯！
Come on, Dennis!
干得好，丹尼斯！
Good work, Dennis!
嘿！跑啊！
Hey! Move along!
你马上就到了
That's it. You're there.
还有六十尺
You're sixty feet.
五十八尺
Fifty... Fifty-eight feet.
可以说是五十六尺半
Call it fifty-six and a half feet...
你就要到了，加油
and you're there. Come on.
这是我伙计！我的伙计！
That's my man! My man!
加油，加油！
Come on, come on!
丹尼斯，加油
Dennis, come on.
趴着吧，踉踉跄跄的
Stay down, you shamble of a man.
别起来
Don't get up.
丹尼斯！
Dennis!
丹尼斯，快，起来
Dennis, come on, get up.
丹尼斯，你马上到终点了，起来
Dennis, you're at the finish line. Get up.
丹尼斯，这姿势不雅，大伙说你呢
Dennis, this looks bad. People are talking.
起来
Get up.
还好吗，丹尼斯？
Hello, Dennis?
-丹尼斯！ -爸！
- Dennis! - Dad!
丹尼斯！
Dennis!
爸！
Dad!
跑！到了！跑！
Go on! You've got it! Go on!
跑啊，丹尼斯！
Come on, Dennis! Yeah!
Yeah!
爸！
Dad!
你这样做真傻
That was a really stupid thing you did out there today.
别去芝加哥
Don't go to Chicago.
爸，你赢了！
Dad, you won!
他成功了！
He's done it!
他真的成功了！
He's actually done it!
今天早上…
This morning...
丹尼斯・道尔还是北伦敦 一位默默无闻的店员
Dennis Doyle was a humble shop worker from North London!
今晚，他已成为英雄
Tonight, he goes home a hero!
Oh, yay.
看啊！
And look at that!
-妈的 -这位伟大的人
- God damn it. - This extraordinary man...
摊倒在了…
collapses into the arms of...
看回放应该是…他心爱的女人怀中
I think it's backwards here... the woman he loves!
看啊！他有个儿子！
And, look! He's got a son!
我不知道他还有个儿子！
I didn't know he had a son!
你知道他有儿子吗？
Did you know he had a son?
-早上好，丹尼斯 -嘿
- Hello, Dennis. - Hey.
-嗨 -嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
杰克，你爸来了！
Jake, your dad's here!
你怎么样？
How's it goin'?
-很好 -好
- Pretty good. - Good.
-你呢？ -好
- You? - Yeah.
不错
Yeah, not bad.
你还跑步吗？
You still running?
每天都跑，希望没跑错方向
Every day, hopefully in the right direction.
Yeah. So...
丽碧，我想…
Um, Libby, I was thinkin', um...
-嗨，爸 -嘿，你呀
- Hi, Dad. - Hey, you.
也没什么
Uh, it doesn't matter, actually.
我…
I'll, um...
我…回头再说
I'll sp... I'll ca... I'll speak to you later.
-好 -跟妈妈再见
- OK. - Say goodbye to your mom.
拜，妈
Bye, Mom.
拜拜，回头见
Bye. I'll see you later.
拜
Bye.
丽碧，不知道你能不能…
Libby, I was wondering, would you like to go...
下周和我一起吃顿饭…
and have some dinner with me next week?
你不一定非得…
You don't have to. It's not, uh...
好
Yeah.
啊？
Uh... huh?
我是说太好了
I mean, wow.
这很好
It'd be nice.
是啊，会很好的
Yeah. Well, it would be.
我…给你打电话
I'll, um... I'll give you a call.
好
OK.
我也不知道做这手势干嘛…
Don't know why I did that. It's just...
好，可以走了？
OK. Ready?
是
Yeah.
好啊！
Hello!
好啊，丹尼斯！
Hello, Dennis!
古先生
Mr G.
-你好，杰克 -你好
- Hello, Jake. - Hello.
我刚从单车课回来
I was just doing my spin class.
很有意思吧
It's great fun, isn't it?
真是很棒的锻炼方法
Oh, it's an amazing workout!
爸爸落后于这位年轻的选手
Dad comin' up behind the young contender.
来！杰克！
Come on! Jake!
他从杰克那儿抢下了球！
Oh, he takes the ball from Jake!
他拿到了球！他无人防守！
He has the ball! He's clear!
爸！传球！
Dad! Pass it!
爸爸无人防守！
Dad is clear!
传啦
Give it!
我再传给你
I'll give you one, too.
好，来，好球
OK, let's go. Good game.
杰克传给古先生
Jake to Mr G.
非常感谢
Yeah, thank you very much.
接球，古先生
Take over, Mr G.
给你，古先生
There you go, Mr G.
好了，我要恶意犯规了
All right, I'm gonna... Completely illegal move there.
举起这位球员，抗着他跑
Picks up the player, runs with him.
扛着他一直跑
Runs with him all the way.
爸，犯规啦！
Dad, that's illegal!
这还没有完
But that's not all.
这人已经不能走路…
Because the guy, he can't barely walk, OK...
更别说跑，但他坚持了…
let alone run, but he keeps going...
二十五里路，拖着扭伤的脚踝
and twenty-five miles on a shattered ankle.
知道他是怎么做到的？
And you know how he did that?
是什么让他坚持下来的？
You know what he said was the one thing...
that kept him going?
是他的教练从没有放弃他
His trainer never gave up on him.
一路陪着他
He stayed with him the whole way.
那人是你？
And that was you?
是啊
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
的确是个好故事
It's a pretty amazing story, actually.
我这儿有些香槟…
I've got a bottle of champagne opened here...
如果你们想继续听的话
if you wanna hear it.
-好 -好
- Sure. - Sure.
那么上来吧
Well, come on up then.
# Aye, aye, aye #
# Everybody #
# Huggin' up the big monkey man #
TLF中文字幕站 http://tlfsubs.eastgame.net
# Aye, aye, aye #
# Everybody #
# Huggin' up the big monkey man #
# Never saw you, I only heard of you #
# I never saw you #
# I only heard of you #
# Huggin' up the big monkey man #
# It's your life #
# Now I know that, now I understand #
# Huggin' up the big monkey man #
# La la la #
# Aye, aye, aye #
# Everybody #
# Huggin' up the big monkey man #
# Aye, aye, aye #
# Everybody #
# Huggin' up the big monkey man #
# Never saw you, I only heard of you #
# I never saw you, I only heard of you #
# Huggin' up the big monkey man #
# It's your life #
# Now I know that, now I understand #
# Huggin' up the big monkey man #
# La la la #
# Keep on runnin' #
# Keep on hidin' #
# One fine day, I'm gonna be the one #
# To make you understand #
# Oh, yeah, I'm gonna be your man #
# Keep on runnin' #
# Runnin' from my arms #
# One fine day, I'm gonna be the one #
# To make you understand #
# Oh, yeah, I'm gonna be your man #
# Hey, hey, hey #
# Everyone keeps talkin' about me #
# It makes me feel so sad #
# Hey, hey, hey #
# Everyone is laughin' at me #
# It makes me feel so bad #
# So keep on runnin' #
# Keep on runnin' #
# Runnin' from my arms #
# One fine day, I'm gonna be the one #
# To make you understand #
# Oh, yeah, I'm gonna be your man #
# Hey, hey, hey #
# Everyone keeps talkin' about me #
# It makes me feel so sad #
# Hey, hey, hey #
# Everyone is laughin' at me #
# It makes me feel so bad #
# So keep on runnin' #
# Runnin' from my arms #
# One fine day, I'm gonna be the one #
# To make you understand #
# Oh, yeah, I'm gonna be your man #
# I'm gonna be your man #